<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kotlin Hyderabad</title>
    <link>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Kotlin Hyderabad</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Kotlin Hyderabad</title>
      <link>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concise Android codebase using Kotlin</title>
      <link>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/talk/concise-android-codebase-using-kotlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/talk/concise-android-codebase-using-kotlin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; slides using Academic&amp;rsquo;s 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; feature and link using &lt;code&gt;slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload&lt;/strong&gt; an existing slide deck to &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embed&lt;/strong&gt; your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further talk details can easily be added to this page using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/slides/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/slides/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;create-slides-in-markdown-with-academic&#34;&gt;Create slides in Markdown with Academic&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Academic&lt;/a&gt; | 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports speaker notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;controls&#34;&gt;Controls&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next: &lt;code&gt;Right Arrow&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous: &lt;code&gt;Left Arrow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start: &lt;code&gt;Home&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish: &lt;code&gt;End&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overview: &lt;code&gt;Esc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaker notes: &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fullscreen: &lt;code&gt;F&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zoom: &lt;code&gt;Alt + Click&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hakimel/reveal.js#pdf-export&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PDF Export&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;code&gt;E&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-highlighting&#34;&gt;Code Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inline code: &lt;code&gt;variable&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Code block:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;porridge = &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;
if porridge == &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;:
    print(&amp;quot;Eating...&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;math&#34;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Block math:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f\left( x \right) = ;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fragments&#34;&gt;Fragments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt; to play!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
One
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
Three
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt;: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;weight&lt;/code&gt;: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;speaker-notes&#34;&gt;Speaker Notes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34;&gt;{{% speaker_note %}}
- Only the speaker can read these notes
- Press `S` key to view
{{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Press the &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;aside class=&#34;notes&#34;&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
  
      
      data-background-image=&#34;/img/boards.jpg&#34;
  &gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-slide&#34;&gt;Custom Slide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34;&gt;{{&amp;lt; slide background-image=&amp;quot;/img/boards.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide background-color=&amp;quot;#0000FF&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide class=&amp;quot;my-style&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-css-example&#34;&gt;Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create &lt;code&gt;assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code&gt; with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-css&#34;&gt;.reveal section h1,
.reveal section h2,
.reveal section h3 {
  color: navy;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://spectrum.chat/academic&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Ask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Condact</title>
      <link>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://kotlinhyderabad.github.in/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This code of conduct is written to guide an individual&amp;rsquo;s choices and actions within the free and open source software (FOSS) community.  This code will help one determine the purpose and the course of his work as well as his place as a member of this community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE ETHIC OF RECIPROCITY
The most fundamental ethic is that of reciprocity&amp;ndash;do unto others as they do unto you.  Are you treating others in a manner that they would not treat you?  If so, then your actions are out of bounds and you should cease those actions.  Emotional reactions should be calculated carefully.  Before acting, decide how the potential response might benefit you and/or the community and how it might hinder you and/or the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACTIONS DEFINE US
People should not be prejudged because of their race, ethnicity, nationality, religious beliefs, gender identity, sexual orientation, age or gender, but rather evaluated on their accomplishments and actions.  Harassment and discrimination should not and will not be tolerated.  Instead, you be judged on your actions. And based on your actions, you will either succeed in your acheivements or fail in your own incompetence or impotence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INEQUALITY
On equality: no two people are the same.  Common sense should dictate that no two individuals have the exact same strength, intelligence, strive to succeed, perserverance, etc.  When you claim that two people are equal, it is insulting to both individuals.  The term inequality should not have a negative connotation; in fact, our inequality should be celebrated.  It is what makes each of us unique.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACCEPTANCE RATHER THAN TOLERANCE
Acceptance is expected among our members, but not necessarily tolerance.  Tolerance is negative in connotation and in practice.  Tolerance is to endure with forbearance and restraint.  It implies that you must fight your own instincts.  Tolerance requires patience and causes stress and frustration.  More importantly, tolerance drains you of your vital energy.  Energy is not limitless so rather than wasting energy on tolerance, direct that energy toward something positive.  Acceptance is a postive emotion and should be practiced by our members.  Where tolerance focuses on the bad aspects of the person or situation, acceptance is seeing the good in the person or situation.  So when you find yourself becoming irritated at the behavior of others, look deeper and find the positive aspects that are there within each of us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DO NOT BE JUDGEMENTAL
The practice of judging and condemning is a negative emotion and is the sign of a shallow intellect.  Typically, the one who is condemning is doing so because of his own inadequacies.  He is weak-minded and must focus on the negative aspects of others to avoid the pain of recognizing the negative aspects of himself.  A wise man once said, &amp;ldquo;Judge not, lest you be judged.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VICTIM MENTALITY AND MARTYRDOM
Some people are habitual victims, seeking personal attention all the time.  When someone is committed to being a victim, everyone else is to blame, and there is absolutely no hope whatsoever for this person.  The victim only has one cause&amp;ndash;himself.  Some victims prefer to play the role of martyr.  They often pick fights in order to lose&amp;ndash;to be the victim, to be the martyr.  Martyrdom is often used by weaklings who cannot admit defeat or admit that they were wrong.  If you are in a situation were martyrdom is your only course of action, then you are championing the wrong cause.  Victim mentality and self-martyrdom will not be tolerated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YOUR VALUE TO THE COMMUNITY
We as human beings tend to over-valuate ourselves, always thinking we are worth more than we actually are.  No one ever claims that they are overpaid or treated too well by others.  We think we are owed.  We are clothed psychologically with pretenses and fraud, but we have to understand that the market is never wrong.  You may think that you deserve more money, greater respect or better treatment.  But if no one is willing to give you these things, then the market has priced you accordingly.  You must learn to evaluate yourself as an impartial observer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COMPETITON IS ENCOURAGED
Competition amongst individuals should not be shunned but encouraged!  The brutal fact is that the more we opt out of competition, the lower our position in the community is likely to be.  If you feel yourself slipping down the ranks of the pecking order, then do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ENFORCING THE CODE OF CONDUCT
The following actions are available to community leaders in the event that disciplinary action needs to be taken:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;VERBAL WARNING
The verbal warning should be a private consultation from a community leader who should explain the violation and prescribe any corrective actions, such as public or private apology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WRITTEN WARNING
The written warning is a formal warning that should be part of the member&amp;rsquo;s permanent record.  The written warning is appropriate if the member being disciplined has already received a verbal warning, or if the offense warrants skipping the verbal warning altogether.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TEMPORARY BAN
The temporary ban should be used for serious violations of the Code of Conduct.  The member being disciplined is banned from any kind of interaction, public or private, with the community for a specified time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PERMANENT BAN
A permanent ban is appropriate when the member being disciplined has proven that he cannot abide by the Code of Conduct.   The member being disciplined is banned from any kind of interaction, public or private, with the community.  This ban is permanent and irrevocable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
